{
    "id": "e40cb1aa8ec44731b5a5c81255c469e5",
    "title": "Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Andy enjoys …………………………. tennis.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "playing",
                "to play",
                "to playing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7940d25ce51c436c85d6220bfedee5eb"
        },
        {
            "question": "Does Sharon …………………………… models from clay?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "make",
                "making",
                "made"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9d758555f7204b99a101c95e3e86e98c"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… holidaying in Toronto, Jane acquired a strong Canadian accent.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "While",
                "Since"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6a4e7638c473445fbfdba585f5451a8c"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………, she could not find her way out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Shocked she was",
                "Shocked she was as",
                "Shocked as she was"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "43810e2df50b4db9951dcd4f5fc9e46f"
        },
        {
            "question": "William ………………………… all the ginger beer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "drinks",
                "drank",
                "drunk"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "32a4a53d831a4fa9953f9a58a0716a76"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her new skirts …………………………. after a week.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "shrink",
                "shrank",
                "shrunk"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c2b5e080c1694581b6900bffaf0d6d57"
        },
        {
            "question": "There …………………………. at the front door.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was anybody",
                "was nobody",
                "wasn't nobody"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7b1c1a3b1906424d831b8e9c81e59e47"
        },
        {
            "question": "Alice says she has already ……………………….. the table.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lain",
                "laid",
                "lied"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7c572067ca9b4e10b317ba0b05e0f552"
        },
        {
            "question": "His old car goes ………………………. but sounds …………………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "quickly noisily",
                "quick noisy",
                "quickly noisy"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "63790bb2ef234fde900ce3e69d457430"
        },
        {
            "question": "Did you do ………………………… in the test after not feeling ………………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good good",
                "well well",
                "good well"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2d46b3c2e81b47269f0bc26beaf2439d"
        }
    ]
}